[
  {
    "id": 390,
    "question": "MySQL supports different Character Sets, which command is used to display all of them?",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "SHOW;  ;"},
      {"id": "B", "text": "None Of The Mentioned"},
      {"id": "C", "text": "CHARACTER SET;"},
      {"id": "D", "text": "SHOW CHARACTER SET"}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_d_correct",
    "tags": ["MySQL"],
    "category": "SQL",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 1024,
    "question": "What does the COPY instruction do in a Dockerfile?",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "COPY makes a copy of your Dockerfile"},
      {
        "id": "B",
        "text": "COPY adds files from your Docker clientâ€™s current directory"
      },
      {"id": "C", "text": "COPY creates a copy of your running container"},
      {"id": "D", "text": "COPY creates a copy of your image"}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_b_correct",
    "tags": ["Docker"],
    "category": "Docker",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 542,
    "question": "Why do we need HTML5 Server-Sent Events?",
    "answers": [
      {
        "id": "A",
        "text": "Server-Sent Events (SSE) is a recent HTML5 specification in combination with the EventSource API designed for streaming updates."
      },
      {
        "id": "B",
        "text": "Server-Sent Events (SSE) is a recent HTML5 specification in combination with the EventSource API designed for getting POST and GET request."
      }
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_a_correct",
    "tags": ["HTML"],
    "category": "Code",
    "difficulty": "Hard"
  },
  {
    "id": 223,
    "question": "Which keyword is used with the UPDATE command to change the value?",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "CHANGE"},
      {"id": "B", "text": "MODIFY"},
      {"id": "C", "text": "ADD"},
      {"id": "D", "text": "SET"}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_d_correct",
    "tags": ["MySQL"],
    "category": "Linux",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 93,
    "question": "Which of the following is used to set cookies?",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "setcookie() function"},
      {"id": "B", "text": "$_COOKIE variable"},
      {"id": "C", "text": "$HTTP_COOKIE_VARS variable"},
      {"id": "D", "text": "isset() function"}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_a_correct",
    "tags": ["PHP"],
    "category": "",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 371,
    "question": "Null is used as a place holder for optional fields",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "True"},
      {"id": "B", "text": "False"}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_a_correct",
    "tags": ["MySQL"],
    "category": "SQL",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 678,
    "question": "In which directory by default user home directories are created?",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "/home"},
      {"id": "B", "text": "/usr"},
      {"id": "C", "text": "/tmp"},
      {"id": "D", "text": "/etc"},
      {"id": "E", "text": "/user"}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_a_correct",
    "tags": ["BASH", "Linux"],
    "category": "Linux",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 635,
    "question": "In which PHP version was 'Final' introduced ?",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "'final' was introduced in PHP5."},
      {"id": "B", "text": "'final' was introduced in PHP7."},
      {"id": "C", "text": "'final' was introduced in PHP6."}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_a_correct",
    "tags": ["PHP"],
    "category": "Code",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  },
  {
    "id": 368,
    "question": "MySQL supports user defined functions",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "True"},
      {"id": "B", "text": "False"}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_a_correct",
    "tags": ["MySQL"],
    "category": "SQL",
    "difficulty": "Easy"
  },
  {
    "id": 833,
    "question": "________is the enterprise-grade cluster management solution from Docker. It manages your whole cluster from a single place.",
    "answers": [
      {"id": "A", "text": "Docker Swarm"},
      {"id": "B", "text": "Docker Compose"},
      {"id": "C", "text": "Docker Universal Control Plane"},
      {"id": "D", "text": "Docker Hub"}
    ],
    "correct_answer": "answer_c_correct",
    "tags": ["Docker"],
    "category": "Docker",
    "difficulty": "Medium"
  }
]
